very good family How are you all
muy buena familia Qué tal estáis
welcome one more day to this humble
bienvenidos un día más a este humilde
channel rumors continue about Fidel
canal continúan los rumores sobre Fidel
and Anabel Dueñas rumors that in
y sobre Anabel Dueñas rumores que para
my opinion have been dragging on since the
mi gusto vienen arrastrándose de la
time of Sálvame when Sálvame was getting along
época de sálvame de cuando sálvame se
great with Rocío Carrasco and they
llevaba a matar con Rocío Carrasco y
put these issues on the table These
ponían estas cuestiones sobre la mesa
are problems that are dragging on and
Son problemas que se están arrastrando y
to this day they are still
a día de hoy pues todavía les están
having consequences before
causando consecuencias antes de
continuing with the video I'm going to ask you
continuar con el vídeo os voy a pedir
please to subscribe activate
por favor que os suscribáis que activéis
the bell well at least
la campanita bueno por lo menos
subscribe okay Now the bell thing
suscribiros vale Ya lo de la campanita
is a little more complicated
lo mejor está un poco más complicado
ladies but the subscribe button is
señoras pero el botón de suscribirse se
very clear okay click there and you
ve muy clarito vale le dais ahí y
become part of this family
entráis a formar parte de esta familia
Anabel Dueñas and Fidel What's
Anabel Dueñas y Fidel Qué es lo que está
going on why are so many people talking about
pasando por qué tanta gente habla de
them and why is it that in
ellos y por qué se sigue adelante en los
recent months they continue with the rumor of a
últimos meses con el rumor de una crisis
relationship crisis between Nivel and Rocío Carrasco
de pareja entre nivel y Rocío Carrasco
whose proof There is none okay because
cuya prueba No hay ninguna vale porque
really it's all speculation and
realmente son todo especulaciones y
gossip people often
habladurías a la gente muchas veces sin
like to give without any proof  to
tener ninguna prueba les gusta dar por
veil something because it is repeated many
velar una cosa porque se repite muchas
times it is worth repeating it many
veces vale como si el repetirlo muchas
times The more they repeat it, the more
veces Cuanto más lo repitan pues las
things become true at the moment
cosas se conviertan en verdad de momento
the only proof there would be Is that the
la única prueba que habría Es que la
people who work at Telecinco are
gente que trabaja en telecinco está
leaking outside the
filtrando fuera de la cadena de
Fuencarral network that lately in the
fuencarral que últimamente en las
last few weeks specifically
últimas semanas en concreto
Fidel would not be accompanying Rocío on
Fidel no estaría acompañando a rociíto a
her program No, you already know that Fidel
su programa No ya sabéis que Fidel
was always like behind the
siempre andaba como detrás de las
scenes not crying laughing giving
bambalinas no llorando riendo dando
instructions hanging out and
indicaciones colegueándose y dándose
hugging David Valdepera and even
abracitos con David valdepera e incluso
Why not say it Anabel
Por qué no decirlo la propia Anabel
Dueñas herself on many occasions she was also
Dueñas en muchas ocasiones también se
behind the cameras I do
encontraba detrás de las cámaras
n't know if they were running the show a bit or
no sé si manejando un poco el cotarro o
well they are like the one that has always been
bueno son como el que siempre ha sido
a couple that they have had like Anabel
una pareja que han tenido como Anabel
as if she were a daughter I mean they are the
como si fuera una hija o sea son la
typical couple that do not have children because they do
típica pareja que no tienen hijos porque
not have them and they take them everywhere to
no los tiene y se llevan a todos lados a
Disneyland and everywhere they take
Disneylandia y a todos lados se llevan
Anabel Dueñas I don't know what would be there not
Anabel dueña no sé lo que habría ahí no
very strange But well the fact that
muy extraño Pero bueno el hecho de que
Fidel was not accompanying Rocío
Fidel no estuviese acompañando a rociíto
to the sets lately  It wouldn't be
a los platós últimamente no sería una
definitive proof to assume and
prueba definitiva para dar por hecho y
assume that
dar por veraz que
Fidel wasn't with Rocío, the
Fidel no estuviera con rociíto ya el
man could already be working,
hombre puede estar trabajando
very good one, eh. Almost to see if he
muy buena esa eh Casi casi a ver si
really could, eh. Wait, they're
realmente podría eh Espera que se van
moving the camera,
moviendo la cámara
okay? Yes, he really could be
vale Sí realmente podría estar
immersed in some project, he could be
inmerso en algún proyecto podría estar
studying because the kid has been
estudiando porque el chaval la ha estado
studying law, I don't know if he'll have to
estudiando derecho no sé si tendrá que
do a master's degree or something to further
hacer algún máster o algo para ampliar
his studies. He could have something to do
sus estudios Podría tener algo que hacer
with his non-livestock companies, no, and I
con sus sociedades no ganaderas no y yo
know how to give
que sé
a shower to the bulls in the field, we do
pegarle una ducha a los toros del campo
n't know about family, but it's not
no sabemos familia pero no es una prueba
irrefutable proof, okay? Let's not cry out to heaven for
irrefutable vale No clamemos al cielo
something that is not yet known, the networks
algo que todavía no se sabe las redes
talk about one thing that has caught
hablan de una cosa que ha llamado la
attention and that is that normally Anabel
atención y es que normalmente Anabel
Dueñas was a person who used to keep
Dueñas era una persona que solía tener
her social networks very updated, she
muy actualizadas sus redes sociales no
wasn't a person who, yes, it's true, she was
era una persona que sí que es verdad era
a person who used to post, Hey, well,
una persona que solía poner Oye pues
this weekend I'm going to sing here. Hey,
este fin de semana voy a cantar aquí Oye
well, look what photo I take with Rocío
pues mira qué foto me hago con rociíto
in the garden. Hey, well, look, I traveled to
en el jardín Oye pues mira he viajado a
Seville and I'm in the Olympic stadium
Sevilla y estoy en el estadio olímpico
and she hasn't posted absolutely anything for exactly 9 weeks,
y lleva exactamente 9 semanas sin poner
nine weeks is a lot, no family, 9
nueve semanas es mucho no familia 9
weeks  without putting absolutely nothing
semanas sin poner absolutamente nada
we're talking about more than two months,
estamos hablando de más de dos meses
about two and a half months, nine weeks without
unos dos meses y medio nueve semanas sin
putting anything, I don't know what you guys think, do you
poner nada no sé qué pensáis ustedes
think it could be due to something
ustedes creéis que se puede deber a algo
strange? There are a lot of people who say that when
raro hay mucha gente que dice que cuando
you go so long without putting anything it's
tú llevas Tanto tiempo sin poner nada es
because you either
porque
have nothing to put because your
o no tienes nada que poner porque tu
life is not interesting or because you do
vida no es interesante o porque
n't want to update your life, no, you don't
no quieres actualizar tu vida no no
want people to know how
quieres que la gente sepa como Cómo
you're doing, okay, I don't know the truth, I mean, they're
andas vale No sé la verdad o sea son
theories, they're very crazy speculations, no,
teorías son especulaciones muy locas no
but well, it is striking, the
pero bueno sí que llama la atención la
truth is that a person who is suddenly so
verdad que una persona de repente tan
active on social media suddenly stops being so
activa en redes de repente deje de serlo
active. Well, the truth is that it is very striking. But well, as I tell you, I believe that on many occasions, and I believe that in most occasions, all of this is nothing more than speculation because there are people who are truly happy about the misfortune of
gente que la verdad se alegran del mal
others, no. And then since they think that
ajeno no Y entonces como piensan que en
Rocío has done a lot of harm to the family
rociíto ha hecho mucho daño a la familia
that they care about or whatever, not to the
que ellos aprecian o lo que sea no a la
family that they like on
familia que ellos les gusta en
television, well, they want to, how would you be
televisión pues quieren como os
happy if things went badly for her in
alegrarían de que a ella le fuera mal en
love? No, you see, the truth is
el amor No ya ves tú a mí la verdad es
that I don't give a damn  and rociíto is with
que me la trae flojas y rociíto está con
noodles she's not there or Fidel was with
fideos no está o Fidel estuviera con
whoever he wanted okay But anyway
quien le diera la gana vale Pero bueno
I tell the rumors that are on
yo cuento Los rumores que hay en
the internet because in my work sincerely there is a lot of talk about this on social networks so I had to tell you remind you that this afternoon remind you that this afternoon I am a guest on the network being a radio on the program cannot be okay I have recorded I will be in the chat
ser vale he grabado estaré en el chat
with you because
con ustedes porque
I would not like to make a reaction and
no me gustaría hacer una reacción y
steal their audience wouldn't it look a little
robarle la audiencia no quedaría un poco
ugly so I have met with the people I have
feo entonces he quedado con la gente he
met with the people I have met with my
quedado con la gente he quedado con mi
community in the chat to be there
comunidad en el chat para estar allí
commenting on the program I don't remember
comentando el programa no me acuerdo
how long it was but I would say that maybe it
cuánto tiempo fue pero yo diría que a lo
was 40 minutes or something
mejor fueron 40 minutos o algo por el
like that
estilo
no more than an hour for sure not Or I
no más de una hora seguro que no O
guarantee that it was not more than an hour
garantizo que más de una hora no fue
but I can tell you that it was
pero sí que os puedo decir que estuvo
very funny that we were laughing
muy divertido que nos estuvimos riendo
a lot and that I am completely sure
mucho y que estoy completamente seguro
that my lordship and my kids are
de que a mi señoría y a mi chavalería
going to like it a lot okay they are going to
les va a gustar un montón vale les va a
like it a lot So at 7 in the
gustar un montón Así que a las 7 de la
afternoon I will wait for you all you can
tarde os espero a todos podéis
listen to it wherever you want you can
escucharlo donde queráis podéis
listen to it on the radio you can listen to it
escucharlo en la radio podéis escucharlo
on Cadena SER you can listen to
en la cadena ser podéis escuchar la
Cadena SER Sevilla you can listen to it on
cadena ser Sevilla podéis escucharlo en
Facebook I think too On
Facebook creo que también En plataformas
digital platforms like Spotify and these things you
digitales así como Spotify y estas cosas
also have no but man on video
también tienes no pero hombre en vídeo
on video so you can see me okay on video you can
en vídeo para que me veáis vale en vídeo
see it on YouTube where they broadcast it also
se ve en YouTube que lo emiten también
okay And I have arranged to meet
vale Y he quedado con las de hecho si os
with the in fact if you go to the channel it can't be okay if you go to their official channel they already have the reminder in case you want to mark it so it will notify you when it starts but we are going at 7 in the afternoon at 7 in the afternoon we will see you on Cadena SER
las 7 de la tarde nos vemos en la cadena
okay on the program it can't be I had a
ser vale en el programa no puede ser me
great time with Julio but I had a
lo pasé muy bien con Julio pero pasé muy
great time with the other guy whose
bien con el otro muchacho que ahora se
name I have forgotten now and he is going to kill me
me ha ido el nombre y me va a matar
Because he also had an arm that was an
Porque además tenía un brazo que era un
Iberian ham no And surely let's see if
jamón ibérico no Y seguramente a ver si
you don't remember his name Javier machaco
no te acuerdas de nombre Javier machaco
[ __ ] no well anyway family
cabrón no bueno en fin familia
What do you think what do you think
Qué pensáis ustedes qué pensáis ustedes
of these rumors about Fidel and about
de estos rumores sobre Fidel y sobre
Anabel Dueñas what do you think about
Anabel Dueñas qué pensáis ustedes sobre
the rumors of breakups between Fidel and
los rumores de rupturas entre Fidel y
Rocío I sincerely  I think that all of these
rociíto yo sinceramente creo que todos
are speculations because I have experienced
son especulaciones porque yo he vivido
many occasions. Well, that both my
en muchas ocasiones Pues que tanto mi
partner and I have a friend in
pareja como yo tengamos una amiga en
common, yes. We have had a friend
común si Nosotros hemos tenido una amiga
in common and we still have one. No, today we
en común y la tenemos no a día de hoy
have two in fact, they are like
tenemos dos de hecho que son como si
sisters and we could go on
fueran hermanas y vamos podríamos irnos
trips with them. Personally, I
de viaje con ellas yo personalmente
could even change clothes in front
podría incluso cambiarme de ropa delante
of them and nothing would happen because
de ellas y no pasaría nada porque
honestly, in my case, they are friends who have been
sinceramente en mi caso que son amigas
since I was little, okay, they are
que son desde que era pequeño vale son
more sisters than friends. No, but hey,
más hermanas que amigas No pero bueno
family, I
familia
will respect your opinion if you have a
respetaré vuestra opinión si opináis
different opinion than me, you will be seeing each other in the
diferente a mí os estaréis viendo en la
comments box, don't forget to
caja de comentarios no olvidéis
subscribe, like, share, see you.
suscribiros darle like compartir nos